## Tigran Khachatryan

tigran.khachatryan.2022@gmail.com
+374 77 87 17 79

Apt. Mikoyan 14/12, Yerevan, Armenia

08 September, 2000

www.linkedin.com/in/khachatryantigran in

github.com/TigranKhachatryan2000 🜎

I am a Front end developer with 2 years of experience who is currently looking for opportunities of implementation of new projects as well of attaining new skills. I have gained a huge developing skills and proficiency in different programming frameworks during my academic and working career. I'd especially underline my abilities of working with JavaScript programing language as I have always been in interaction with projects containing those frameworks. My services are fast and reliable. You can contact me any time. Thank you for your interest.

### EDUCATION SK

Bachelor

### National Polytechnic University of Armenia

09/2018 - 06/2024 Armenia/Yerevan Courses

- Information Systems

### Master's degree

National Polytechnic University of Armenia

09/2024 - Present Armenia/Yerevan Courses

 Informatics and Applied Mathematics

# Introduction to React and Node.js Armenian Code Academy

09/2021 - 03/2022

Armenia/Yerevan

- Courses
- Started learning Programing basics
- Create a Web application using React and Redux
- Learned how to work with team.

**SKILLS** 

React	• • • • •
JavaScript	••••
Node.js/Express.js	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Redux/Retux Toolkit	• • • • •
HTML/CSS/SASS/Bootstrap	• • • • •
GIT/GitLab/Azure	• • • • •
C++/OOP	
SQL/Mongo DB	

### **LANGUAGES**

Russian Professional Working Proficiency English
Professional Working
Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Chess | Sports | Books | Music | Films

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

React Developer

Rocket Systems 03/2022 – 05/2022

Armenia/Yerevan

Web and Mobile Development

Soft Construct

06/2022 – Present Armenia/Yerevan

Web and Mobile Development